Okay now I am going to show you the materials that you need to assemble to make this project.
It's probably the most complicated part of it because you need quite a few different things.
You need a sixteenth centimeters of antique cooper chain.
It's a small chain, it's not too bulky.
You could use, that's about four inches, obviously this depends on how long you wish to wear your necklace, so you could start with it a little bit longer then cut it shorter at the end.
You cut chain, chain is sold in long spools and you cut it using a pair of wire cutters.
Never cut chain with scissors because it breaks the scissors, that's by the way.
And then you need three flower pieces which are with the holes that you embellish.
You can get these from specialized jewelry stores.
And you need four millimeter, five millimeter crystals depending on, the size is really a question of taste.
These happen to Austrian crystals.
You can use Swarovski crystals and I would say the color of the crystal depends on the color combination you are going to chose for you necklace.
You need four jump rings.
Smallest jump rings, these are about eight millimeters.
And four rounded head pins and you need of course Swarovski crystals, the size is known as twenty-four PP.
And if you see, these crystals are going to be inserted in these little holes here and the one in the middle is actually a little bit bigger.
So if you really want to be exact, this is an eighteen PP hole but the twenty-four does fit in it, it's just a little bit smaller.
And you need and antique cooper lobster clasp.
And once you have got all of these products assembled then you are ready to begin.
In addition to the wire cutters that you need for cutting the chain, you need two pairs of flat nose pliers and a pair of needle nose pliers, in order to work with the necklace.
You will need special glue called Strass 244, which is for glueing on the crystals.
And it's advisable to have a Q-Tip at your disposal and a little bit of water.